有谁看见玛蒂了么
Has anybody seen Maddie?
比赛还有两分钟就开始了
Our game starts in two minutes.
玛蒂还没有来
Maddie's not here?
她可从来没有缺席过一场比赛的啊
She's never missed a game.
等等  要是玛蒂没有来  我就得上场了啊
Wait, if Maddie doesn't show, that means I have to play.
这可不能这样啊  天
That can't happen, man.
我本来还打算在比赛的时候把作业写了呢
During the game is when I get my homework done.
玛蒂今天表现的很是奇怪啊
Maddie was acting really weird today.
她是不是长高了
And did she get taller?
长高了
Taller?
大概长高了多少  是不是 7 公分左右
Like how much taller? Like 2 1/2 inches taller?
差不多吧
Yeah, something like that.
她看上去变了个人似的
She just seemed different.
她居然在那咯咯笑  玛蒂才不会这么笑
She giggled. Maddie doesn't giggle.
她一直都是哼哼的
She snorts.
她今天整个感觉都像是由内而外透出某种光芒似的
It's like she had some kind of inner sparkle, man.
鞋子
The shoes.
我想我应该知道她在哪里了
Um, I think I know where she might be.
我这就去叫她
So I will just go get her.
嗯
Yeah.
你看看能不能把表演拖一会
See if you can get them to hold curtain.
天  这姑娘真心不了解运动啊
Wow, that girl really doesn't get sports.
好吧  小污点  该你上场了
All right, stains. You're in.
好吧
Fine.
我又不知道今天要我上场
I didn't think I was going to play today.